This particular color that we chose for Myra's hair, actually requires a heat process.
So, in this process I need to clip the hair off of her neck.
I'm going to cover her neck with a towel.
So, we don't get hair color all over her skin.
We're actually going to cover her with a plastic cap.
Making sure that the hair is covered, but not the skin.
Because, remember every place that hair color touches it's going to stain the skin.
So, we don't want any extra stained skin.
So, we've covered her with a plastic bag.
We're going to set a timer.
She actually processes for ten minutes. Set my timer. And, this particular color process requires heat. So, we're going to put Myra under the heat for ten minutes.
And, as soon as her processing time is over I don't need to do a test strand on this whatsoever.
When you're applying color, you just follow the direction.
And, process it as the directions explain for you to do.